nlbuysell.com 2017-07-15

# Buy & Sell Privacy Policy - NL Buy Sell - Online & Offline

This document was last modified on February 6th, 2016.

At the Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online we recognize that privacy is important. This Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by the Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online or its subsidiaries.

If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or [email](mailto:privacy@nlbuysell.com) us.

The Buy & Sell Website uses cookies to help show you more relevant ads on the webpages. Third party vendors also use this data to show more relevant ads throughout the internet based on your past visits to websites. If you would like to Opt-out of this tracking, please [click here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

At the Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online we recognize that privacy is important. This Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by the Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online or its subsidiaries.

If you have any questions about this policy, please feel free to contact us.

## Information we collect and how we use it:

We offer a number of services that do not require you to register or provide any personal information to us, such as horoscopes. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

**Information you provide:** When you sign up to purchase the Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online online, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address, credit card and an account password). Credit card information is not stored in any location and only used for the purchase of the Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online Online.

**User communications:** When you send email or other communication to the Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

**Other sites:** This Privacy Policy applies to web sites and services that are owned and operated by the Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online. 

The Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online only processes personal information for the purposes described in the applicable Privacy Policy and/or privacy notice for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include:

  * Providing our products and services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising;
  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and
  * Developing new services. 

The Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online processes personal information on our servers in Canada. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our financial institution.

## Choices for personal information

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. 

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent.

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case the Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online may not be able to provide those services to you.

## Information security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to the Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

## Data integrity

The Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

## Accessing and updating personal information

When you use the Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete users' personal information.

## Enforcement

The Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or the Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online's treatment of personal information by contacting us through this web site or by writing to us at

Privacy Matters  
c/o The Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online Inc.  
50 O'Leary Avenue  
P.O. Box 8512, Station A  
St. John's, NL  
A1B 3N9  
Canada

When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is the Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online's policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between the Newfoundland Buy & Sell Online and an individual.

## Changes to this policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date.
